Welcome to 6.390!
Jump into the learning where the algorithms group.
Supervised. Unsupervised.
Let's find our rhythm and move on.
Let's dive into the data. Find the stories we can tell with six three nitinol knowledge.
We're under a machine learning spell. Linear, non-linear will dance through every way.
Gradient descent is our partner, taking us to sway from theory to the practice.
We'll navigate the scene in the land of algorithms.
We'll build our dream machine. Oh, welcome to 630.
Gotta do where the excitement flows. With every model built, we're ready to break those codes.
Reinforcement learning is calling. Let's get up on our feet.
With funky neural networks, we can't be beat.
I.